<resources>
    <string name="help_sms_content_filter">
        <![CDATA[
        These rules apply to the SMS message content.<br>
        <br>
        <font color="#ffa500"><b>Note</b></font>: For SMS messages, this app works as an \"addon\" of the default SMS app, it blocks notifications instead
          of blocking messages, spam messages will still be present in the default SMS app. <font color="#fa7f71"><b>Disable</b></font> the notification of the default
          SMS app in system settings, let this app take over the notification, otherwise there will be double notifications. <br>
        <br>
        The list is <b>displayed</b> in descending order of priority, ascending description, and ascending pattern. <br>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_quick_copy">
        <![CDATA[
        A quick way to copy content from SMS messages, such as verification codes. <br>
        <br>
        When it matches, a button like <font color="yellow"><b>Copy: 123456</b></font> would appear in the notification. <br>
        It is not like clicking on the notification, when the copy button is clicked, only this notification is dismissed, other notifications will remain. <br>
        <br>
        A sample rule: (using capturing group) <br>
        &emsp; <font color="cyan"><b>code.*?(\\d+) </b></font><br>
        Another approach: (using lookaround) <br>
        &emsp; <font color="cyan"><b>(?&lt;=code.{0,3})\\d+</b></font><br>
        &emsp;<font color="#ffa500"><b>Note</b></font>: <br>
        &emsp; It does not support <font color="#fa7f71"><b>.*</b></font> in lookarounds, it requires a bounded max length.<br>
        &emsp; for example, use: <b>(?&lt;=code</b><font color="cyan"><b>.{0,3}</b></font><b>)\\d+</b> <br>
        &emsp; instead of: <b>(?&lt;=code</b><font color="#fa7f71"><b>.*</b></font><b>)\\d+</b> <br>
        <br>
        It only works when the SMS message is <b>NOT</b> <font color="#fa7f71"><b>blocked</b></font>.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_apply_to">
        <![CDATA[
        Uncheck these checkboxes to disable this rule for Call, SMS, or both.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_importance">
        <![CDATA[
        None: No notification at all. <br>
        Shade: The dropdown notification shade. <br>
        StatusBar: The small icon in the top bar. <br>
        Sound: The default notification sound. <br>
        Heads-Up: Popup a floating window on the top of the screen.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_test_rules">
        <![CDATA[
        This helps to check if the rules are set as expected.<br>
        <br>
        It is just a simulation and will not actually popup an incoming call(or text message).<br>
        <br>
        The result is shown here, and in history log, with notification.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_test_quick_copy">
        <![CDATA[
        This is not a simulation, it only shows if any quick-copy rule matches the content.<br>
        <br>
        To simulate receiving, use the <font color="cyan"><b>Test</b></font> from <font color="#0000ff"><b>Message Rules</b></font> instead.
        ]]>
    </string>

</resources>