<resources>
    <string name="api_preset_groq">Groq</string>
    <string name="help_api_preset_groq">
        <![CDATA[
        Check the SMS content using <b>Groq AI</b>, it only requires an email account.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_api_preset_groq_authorization">
        <![CDATA[
        1. Register and login: <br>
         <a href="https://console.groq.com/login">https://console.groq.com/login</a><br>
         <br>
        2. Open the API page:<br>
         <a href="https://console.groq.com/keys">https://console.groq.com/keys</a><br>
        <br>
        3. Press the <translate>\"Create API key\"</translate> button.<br>
        <br>
        4. Copy the key, then fill it in below.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="spam_sms_prompt_template">
        Categorize this SMS message as Political, Fraud, Survey, or Marketing.
        If none applies, answer \"Valid\", otherwise, answer the category only, don\'t answer anything else.
        The SMS message is:
        {escape({sms})}
    </string>
    <string name="spam_sms_negative_category"><translate>(Political|Fraud|Survey|Marketing)</translate></string>
    <string name="spam_sms_positive_category">Valid</string>
    <string name="last_log">Last Log</string>
    <string name="executed_at">Executed at:</string>
    <string name="not_executed_yet">Not executed yet</string>
    <string name="rule_indicator">Rule Indicator</string>
    <string name="help_show_rule_indicator">
        <![CDATA[
        Show icons before the number to indicate whether it exists in the spam database or is there any regex rule that matches it. <br>
        <br>
        At a quick glance, you can effortlessly verify if the history records are covered by the rules, so you don\'t need to test them individually. <br>
        <br>
        <font color="#ffa500">Note:</font><br>
        This can impact the performance when there are too many regex rules. <br>
        <br>
        <b>Examples:</b> <br>
        <br>
        <img src=\'ic_history_indicator_1\'/> <br>
        &ensp; - The first green number icon indicates this number will be allowed by a number rule. <br>
        &ensp; - The second red SMS icon indicates this SMS content will be blocked by a content rule. <br>
        &ensp; - The third red database icon indicates this number exists in the spam number database. <br>
        <br>
        These icons are arranged by <font color="#ea86ff"><b>priority</b></font>, the <b>first</b> icon indicates
        the overall result. That number rule has a higher priority, the SMS message will eventually be allowed by it.<br>
        <br>
        <img src=\'ic_history_indicator_2\'/> <br>
        &ensp; - It will be allowed by a content rule. <br>
        &ensp; - It will be blocked by a number rule. <br>
        &ensp; - it exists in the spam number database. <br>
        <br>
        The <b>first</b> icon indicates the message will eventually be allowed by the content rule.<br>
        <br>
        <img src=\'ic_history_indicator_3\'/> <br>
        No number rule matches it, only SMS rule and database. And it will be blocked by an SMS rule.<br>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_enable_for_mms">
        <![CDATA[
        MMS messages are usually spam, it\'s unnecessary to be enabled unless you actually use them.<br>
        <br>
        <font color="#ffa500">Note:</font><br>
        Group messages are MMS, not SMS.<br>
        <br>
        MMS will be treated as SMS, only text content will be processed,
        multimedia content, such as image and audio, will be ignored.<br>
        <br>
        Two permissions are required: RECEIVE_MMS and READ_SMS
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="unknown_error">Unknown error.</string>
    <string name="checking_auth_credential">Checking authorization credentials.</string>
    <string name="sms_bomb"><short>SMS Bomb</short></string>
    <string name="help_sms_bomb">
        <![CDATA[
        Anti SMS Bombing.<br>
        <br>
        Prevent massive, continuous floods of SMS messages, which are often composed primarily
          of OTP (One-Time Password) verifications.<br>
        <br>
        For example, SMS messages like:<br>
        &ensp; <font color="#888888">Your OTP is: 1234.</font><br>
        &ensp; <font color="#888888">This is your verification code: 1234.</font><br>
        &ensp; <font color="#888888">1234 is your validation code.</font><br>
        <br>
        <h5><font color="#00BFFF">- Content regex</font></h5>
        This feature applies only to messages that match this regex, a typical regex would be: <br>
        <font color="#fa7f71">.*(otp|code).*</font><br>
        <br>
        <h5><font color="#00BFFF">- Interval</font></h5>
        If a subsequent OTP message arrives within this time interval, it is considered
          part of the bombing attack and will be blocked.<br>
        (default: 30 seconds)<br>
        <br>
        This will block all following bombs, except for the first one.<br>
        <br>
        <h5><font color="#00BFFF">- Lockscreen protection</font></h5>
        Enable this to block all bombs in lockscreen mode, including the first one. <br>
        <br>
        Usually, your screen should have been unlocked while waiting for a verification code.
        When such messages arrive while the device is in lockscreen mode, they are likely to be bombs.<br>
        <br>
        <font color="#ea86ff"><b>Priority: 20</b></font>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="lockscreen_protection"><short>Lockscreen protection</short></string>
    <string name="help_history_logging">
        <![CDATA[
            When disabled, calls and SMS messages will not be logged and will not be displayed here.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_history_expiry">
        <![CDATA[
            When enabled, history records will expire after N days, expired records will be deleted automatically.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="never_expire"><short>Never Expire</short></string>
    <string name="enable_history_logging">Log</string>
    <string name="help_rcs_message">
        <![CDATA[
            RCS is not supported.<br>
            <br>
            Despite being a standard protocol, RCS is implemented differently by each messaging app.<br>
            <br>
            A workaround is to switch to SMS.
        ]]>
    </string>
</resources>